What the fuck is this?
This is Kailos.
His new model looks so good, man.
I did not expect to see you again so soon, my friend.
After you'd answered the call of the irons.
Something has happened, Katkar.
Something terrible.
Kalakos, tell me.
It all happened so quickly.
And Rathien, young as he is, bravely or perhaps foolishly tried to stop it.
But he was too late.
Did you hit him in the head with a rock?
The tempest.
Oh shit.
We should have killed him.
Oh, here we go.
Oh.
It's a rock guy from the cinematic Stonebrow.
Who is she?
What is she?
She is Razageth, youngest of the primal Incarnates.
Incarnates?
Four dangerous adherents of the elemental forces.
At the dawn of the aspects, our flights embraced the titans gifts.
They did not.
The war that followed was unimaginable.
And it took all of our strength combined to banish them.
If they were so dangerous, why were they not destroyed?
I hadn't the heart to do it.
We were once as clutchmates.
So it's her sister.
Time, it seems, has not quelled their fury.
And look at us.
Should she free her kin now, we haven't the strength to stop them.
And if Iridicrum's hunger is unleashed.
Then we have no choice.
If we are to be protect us once more, the aspects of our dragon flights must be made anew.
So they're going to undo that cataclysm shit?
Our queen is determined, Kedgar.
But we've only just begun to find who we are again.
And I fear that without help, we may never get the chance to see our future secured.
Hmm.
This is staff.
Then it seems the mortal races too must answer the call and face the storms ahead.
That's a good, that's a good one. Yeah.